[Applause] current coyote 3 to one coyotes dancing
coie scores what a goal by the youngster look at
this I mentioned earlier that he's a dancer watch
the dance move right there and then gets himself
in a position when he spins the second time
he's in a perfect shooting position and he
and he goes where to the right wing turns his back
takes the shot and SC look how far he changes the
angle when he has it on his back hand and then the
perfectly placed shot below the blocker above the
pad almost impossible to stop great play there by
C he heads off for a new stick Jack F swooping in
sharp angle SC Lo close your side door and if you
don't the elite players like Jack Hughes will take
advantage of that daylight as he did there what a
play by Jack Hughes dropped for nander he assisted
on the power play go in scy this is just the end
of a period and a player just taking the game
into his own hands nice job of Kamar taking a body
with him once he sees the middle taken away gets
it to the outside uses his Edge as well and gets
it around gersson he realizes he has some space
hands it off to peton back to Garland and what
a beautiful goal the first goal of the season
for the Vancouver canuts off the Stick of
Conor Garland and puts a beautiful move on
this bouncing Puck that gets by Bret kulak it's
a l little bouncer that finds him right on the
stick and quick hands in tight by Garland goes
to the backand elevates for a one- nothing lead
three by Kane and now McDavid what a spin the
recovery the shot SC he goes down spinorama
pops back up and somehow that puck was loose I
mean that is absolute nightmare for that puck
to be ahead of him when he gets up but he attacks
with so so much speed doesn't even miss a beat and
then buries it on the Breakaway wow it's like a
whacka you thought he was gone and he just popped
right back up come on it's just unfair Anderson
on the Pu waits to stay outside plays it for
cop Anderson does a nice job of coming across
the Blue Line holding on to it so Coffield can
get into place slides it over to him what
a nice move on the rookie cinsky although
he doesn't get in across he gets to the inside
of his backand gets it upstairs Michael on the
dying seconds of the period now trying to
dance his way through and scores oh what a
goal what a play by eel late here on the first
a little bit of Juggle as he goes across it's
a loose pop through two guys and gas tries to
play stick on Stick that's not going to work
and it's a power move and that just s hands
in tight as he goes to the forand stall had
to go off replaced him M with a short move SC
look at mckin spinning on the wall watch the
back door right off the skat of Ryan Johansson
and that's a good goal all day long no kicking
motion you're allowed to deflect and what a
sweet play byan mckin throwing it onet bit of
a lucky break oh I say Ryan Johansson
knew exactly what he was doing Kaden
Primo mat cutting it to the for score what
a goal terrific read of the situation by
Mike Masson he understood the overplay he took
advantage it he went the other way split Sean
ther and John Marino right down the middle and
want to finish VCH van through the fiveo otter
stumbles es Gates of Carlton center circle
otter back on his blad with speed between the
legs Paul Conor shows off the hands wow C
fakes the shot between the legs you see as
soon as he fakes that shot it forces Zula to
stand up straight as he stands up straight it
goes between the legs with it puts it Far Side on
heart and wow is the only word here's feno SC and
a dart to the top of the net yeah was that ever
Ken what a move by number 90 there in red in an
absolute perfect shot and the wings are back
in business who's picked up an assist already
tonight tip score shot by Dean tipped by asimon he
battles for everything and this is a battling goal
kind of a typical one for asimon even though he's
getting jumped from behind at the last sck and by
Hoffman he gets a stick on it and he redirects
that that was nasty for the goenda no chance on
that one besser dumps one ahead hoping Miller
can get there first he does he scores what a
play by Brock besser to angle that one off the
cornerboards Miller there puts it home in the
back hand and the Canucks have a two nothing
lead Miller's in behind everybody right up
top backand chip two goals for the Canucks two
Power Play Goals for the Canucks after that so
Dash by Fabian zerland here's Pon at the
offensive Blue Line cuts across Fe Susi
nice pass but C scores Carson Susi put it on the
tape after Pon is able to Bobble a puck off the
blade of his stick move it across and odman Rush
turns into the fifth goal of the hockey game for
the Canucks quick outlet and up the eight comes
acont AC up the middle what a go here comes aimon
up the middle he wants to pass it back and he's
actually trying to make a play into the middle of
the ice and he's getting knocked down in the back
hand and it ends up going top shelf here's Crosby
stepping ahead of the pack drops it for tank back
header score absolutely sick from the Pittsburgh
Penguins eyes in the back of his head senses going
off like crazy it's like he knows where Chris L
Tang is he knows where everybody is Josh three gie
takes the shot and Gallagher's in front kcks it
knocks it down and then slides it around he is so
good at getting body position the reach he's able
to steer it in padar takes the puck scores what a
goal by Conor Bard how did he do that what a steal
far down not even looking he makes the goenda
think that he's going to pass it and just puts
it in Beauty here a chance for skner now catching
up to the puck on a break Bo skner deep score
just skner pick it off in motion and able to get
separation and when he does he just puts a quick
little to move you see how he got back on his
heels and escape and changed Direction real quick
as soon as he started making the move towards
the net got right on the heels right there and
look at how quick those feet were cuner had zero
chance on that one it's picked up by cadri cadri
in with a power move to the SLO and the scores
cadri great move off the board did a wonderful
job of protecting the pck cadri fortunately
for cadri he's able to rip that one by monmo
gra one timer over the head of luk is put inny
with some absolute sorcery from the quter when
you least expect it the bank in from the bad angle
off the helmet on a one-time on the backand that
just like the Predators do a smashville for work
busts in drags and holds he shoots oh what a great
individual effort there by Philip forsberg
to create that scoring chance watch this tow
drag watch how far he brings his but back slides
to the middle forsberg just puts her five hole
what a beauty finding in his tippet moves around
vron in go he SC oh and TI dazzles on his way in
he's on the off Wing So when he takes it to his
forehand he's got a lot of net to work with boy
what a play and what a finish by tippet Matthews
r on ahead knock down loose Puck goes to neand
rning in score highlight re stuff from William El
that acceleration out of a pile and then the stke
shrugs off Anderson Anderson puts a stick on him
doesn't impact him all pulls it around bdar and
Tucks it home beautiful goal TI that head for
stla winding it is Tim stla L The Edge speeds
it back K scores what a feed by stla and K's got
his second this is a crazy play they probably
should have been a penalty called to to break it
and when everybody had their back turned I mean
this is a pass and a half right onto the tape of
kachuck who goes whoa look what I got and he says
thank you very much oh Sanders drops it back in
com to pass he BS it in t an incredible forwa oh
what a goal he's got to wait for it to drop and
he does weighs TI chokes down on the blade more
control and fats it past a crawling James Rymer
home run swing walk off is what it is for Tim C
oh that's brilliant second left in overtime pulls
up waiting for some help now into the Dallas h
fell down eel has the puck TR a move it lost
it gets it back eel scores Jack eel stayed
with it and wins in an overtime wow I going to
give a little side appreciation note to Alex
petrangelo for holding the line he ended up in the
splits almost but eel well he initially loses the
puck which leads to a fantastic goal at the end a
little bit of luck and out of the Zone it goes yes
pulled ahead by elers oneon-one Nikolai eers HS a
through gets around and he shoots and scores this
doesn't happen without the brilliant little give
at the defensive Blue Line look at that little
one touch from Peretti into the Wheelhouse for
eers good pick up little inside out as he dances
around the defender but speed is his weapon and
when you combine it with those kind of silky Mets
to the top Corner what a dangerous player what
a dangerous play shks have had the lead twice
here's grin in he's SC what a goal by me KY grin
his first do a Shar and it's a beauty comes up
with speed attacks the middle good move the inside
protects the part pushes the stick away takes it
right to the hole puts it in what a big lift for
the Sharks as Michael took that pass away Savers
get it back again here's Benson in front what a
move scores Zack Benson with his first NHL goal
and that is a beauty to remember for all time
this is total confidence going to the front of
the net and he pulls his back between his legs
he's going to put right up top underneath the
bar No Way Camper expecting this and look at how
easy it was just simple effective and clean in a
break away oh hello hello oh baby what a pass by
Marty NES to Stephan unselfish probably could have
went back shelf just drop it just take a tap in
my light and the little chip from Nason to make
sure that comy doesn't make a spectacular low sa
but you think about NES hasn't scored in some time
he could have taken that to the house completely
so especially when you consider the circumstance
tonight he's had a lot of them here now more
spinning shooting sces there was absolutely no
space Oh yes there was there's no waste of
time there's no hesitation it's skill it's
power oh my up the side of the doget got to the
of scores does that go between his legs I mean
he's he's facing the wrong way Lon is just going
to throw this at the net watch the hand ey he's
going to spin back between his legs what a goal
on for Robbie P right a goal last night nice move
there P right in go oh he scored what a play oh
my goodness that's a good example of playing the
puck and not the body and Robbie Fab made him pay
did he undress him or what as I look at the big
board there's a jock trrap hanging on it and it
belongs to Kaiser oh my jackets come up with the
puck oh nice move there and then fantelli after
beating he goes between the legs and the jackets
then Tilly scores then he starts and finishes the
play what a great individual effort by the rookie
F whoa between the legs and then Kent Johnson how
about the skill on this line Kent Johnson bats it
out of the air gets it on his stick and it's a
double clutch and fanly says get me that Puck
and there whips it yeah that's got to feel good
here's the red hot Zack hman holds his last nine
and make it 10 what a goal by zackman your little
button hook spin by himman he looks up and says
I'm taking this one to the pose and that's exactly
what he did jams it Far Side protecting the oh my
goodness from the back hand to the forehead that's
a brilliant play there byman mman up for melli to
[Music] Moser now machell to the Middle melli With
A Chance and a goal home and it's Michael Carone
unbelievable Matias machell how you doing and
look at this movement machell just says follow me
boys he throws it at the cage and he finds Michael
carcone oh what a play that is DAV steel down the
middle ditch hman hatrick some kind of look by the
captain and Hyman got a hatrick of hat tricks for
his career what a pass at the end of this great
individual effort little pickpocket spin undresses
a hurricane and then finds himman knows where he
is which is the incredible part for Conor McDavid
as the hats come funneling down onto the ice tyru
move to the middle wide open he scores oh what a
play unbelievable goal by kyou good passing sets
this up right here Jordan Kyrie the old Shak and
bake to the middle of the ice and how you going
it's in the back of the netan Hopkins speaking
about pass McDavid Cuts in wait Waits it home
Conor McDavid a virtuoso game time goal watch
this paent stick handles thick handle get flurry
to bite you know Mark Andre flurry's an aggressive
golender wants to come out and challenge that's
exactly what he does with the patience the skill
of Conor McDavid to walk this around tuck it
home on the backhand side absolutely ridiculous
goal away comes Matthews drops it back to Dand
neander winds in still has a knan fe it back
across Matthew two scores Austin Matthew elander
who dances right through the SE all by himself and
Matthews who hasn't had a lot of success against
the gets one by him but smart well aware play by
the fourth Lin he get out of the way let the
first liners go to work and now CRA trying to
pull away n COV up the middle one-on-one with
CC scores what a goal look at him fight through
literally fight through to get to this pu Cero's
concentration on the puck is simply outstanding
here's kavaris 1,1 points centering Mur back
score tamarus with that open Ice he's got two
guys collapsing on him able to keep it alive but
how the patience of mar but it was just perfectly
executed around the stick right through the five
hle Willam me at a 19 point streak Matthew scor
number 26 and he's scoring every way possible what
a sick play that is on the sideboard looked like
it as he was coming around he might go back
to the point Levi definitely didn't expect
it what a move by CZ oh go by John tovares one
of the things that tovares works on a lot those
little tight turns but there's two beauties and
just a perfect shot and his son here Matias Oh
What a Beautiful backand by marenko is back to
the play and just whipped a wicked backhander
he's going to have that time and space and not
only is it a back I think it's a forehand Jeff
pulls it between the legs and roof it's between
two sets of legs actually Bard shoots wide
the stick side of Bennington KF plays the rebound
for Bard down low Bard thecross stle scores what
a play I don't believe what I just saw other
worldly skill here as he just softly picks
that up on his stick goes up over the shoulder
he knew exactly what he's going to do takes it
off the board protects it and reversed it in as
a right hand shot and tucked it by the glove we
have not seen him do that in a game situation
just yet but the kids got some marvelous hands
dude that was insane then yov brings it back in
drops it off to zis Trevor takes it in behind
the net he scores on the cross goal the thing
about zis when he does this and executes it is
he's moving I've seen a lot of guys try it but not
while they're skating at almost full speed what a
beautiful play by Tripp Seekers I think most of
the crowd is just now realizing what he did cuz
they showed the replay a couple of times on the
big board above Center ice and the reaction got
a great deal louder DeAndre Miller take tapes a
niy across the line rink wide hoping for crrider
he'll put it behind the n z a one touch back off
what a play by Ma zabad you cannot one touch a
pass prettier than that the rim comes around he
angles his stick knows wheeler here and he leaves
it right on the tape and Blake wheeler loves
it Jack Hughes Luke Hughes jper brat all on
the ice Luke all the way through he scores Luke
goes coast to coast and ties it are you kidding
me what a burst of speed look Hughes just Barrel
through a couple of Columbus Blue Jackets look
at this Baro to thrun passing the high slot
picked off here's a break fala can even the
score DS scores watch The Finisher by Kevin I
mean this is just pure skill stick what oh M he
probably made five stick handles and then at the
end watch this over the pad blocker wasn't there
beat the goal Center King tight up one to one
for the first time of the period but last long
Z chips to far now connect connect the dles got
it in front and scor my goodness here's a skill
little backand tow drag and the will to take it
to the blue paint and he's going to the net hard
and as he does that puck just rolls off his stick
and Fool's terar off for the head pass up to Hegel
Hegel Cuts in St St what a great set of hands by
Brandon Hegel and he had to fight his way with the
puck through traffic that was simply outstanding
spinning around that is a beautiful little move
look like they might have a chance to pick it off
and go with numbers the other way here's sud in P
Suter across nice move by hoglander he scores
NS hoglander between the legs and a backhander
along the ice su's going to hold it and then find
hoglander between the legs and between the legs
just stking forberg he's been long up Hallberg
shov a go score oh what h p Holberg with his first
goal in 19 games you'd never know it that is nice
the strength get the leg out how low there are no
passengers in this game for either team here's
Patterson in Le P nice move stop getes a rebound
tcks it in what a play Patterson with the dangles
the shot the rebound and the Finish sent off by
gets it back holds it back pocket skips it gets
it and as he's getting knocked to the ice the
wherewithal to go below the goal line above the
goal line with that stick in the net have to go
in this maea in the nation's capital CU Nets off
it's bed in Nick Dow K Nets off gets outside of
the defense and as he flips it to the net Nick Dow
is going to tap this just below shoulder height
this is a good goal to connect me he chip it but
H the L with it's got back by tippet it across the
line tippet dances his way in the back Henry scor
a thing of beauty you got to be kidding me what a
move by tippet tippet picks it up absolutely walks
Justin F what a move a delayed penalty was going
to be called but the backhand finished by tippet
wow dealing with Json with a backand wide of the
goal here's Kenco around the Chicago net out
the near side Andre Keno SP on score and that
emotional reaction was a thank you to kco for a
spinning pass through the slot and all soon had
to do was pop it in to make it one nothing this is
what kco can do so well get some separation eyes
to the back of the head the old spinner soon
burries it as moric stretches across and goes
under him remaining in the second pelski Robertson
his shot he scores the defenses of the Islanders
at times have looked like they're thinking more
than doing Stars used that to their advantage just
squeeze it into the slot the slice slippery play
of Jason robertsson and a tie hockey game Le now
with 94 Point chance fromont scores Matthews
just following in middle and how about these
hands between the legs and Joey dor tried to get
that left pad out as far as he could but look at
the patience by Matthews Flyers break it up Frost
holding on slips it across for York York the shot
blocked and then he BS it and he scores little
baseball skill from Cav YK backand out of it
there and pass baseski following that part all the
way around waits till it gets below the crossbar
that's what amazes me and he sees it the whole
time whacking that thing top shelf what a beauty
here's a guy that can scoop to n eers breaking
in on shik to the backand scor and how about
this individual effort head up flying a little
move there dances around shik kicks it to a stick
and then that beautiful backand as well to finish
off just inside the post and had a lot of mustard
it as well FS that back kicked away picked up by
Matthews in scor this is the brilliant of Austin
Matthews he just jumps on this loose Puck that's
not clear drags it through his legs and that rer
as good as there is Greer's trying to dump it in
he gets kick back towards him keeps it on S side
squats it has that touch through his legs then
away from Oly and straight into the Wheelhouse to
beat Vadar in with more chances nice drag gorgeous
move a shot score a thing of beauty from Wyatt
Johnston that goes go straight to the Highlight
Reel well Wyatt went be back here he just tow
drag loses one fights off a check and then with
do in full Retreat is able to slip it past the
glove oh and tippet turbocharge time tippet spins
back at he SC and tip it absolutely dazzling oh
my goodness what a goal I thought he'd go wide
additionally he goes wide cuts to the middle and
and this is a hot nasty spinorama six school
backand lovsky has got it here eyes lovsky will
dump it in out of the net his dods merer after
iteld knocks it out of the air lovsky scores what
a setup by Cole Coffield and SL kovski finishes
it watch Coffield turn the stick over in midair
and bat it backwards with the toe you know he gets
in the comfort spot and he puts it right onto the
Stick of slap kovski back to Center ice it goes
sha n will look to move it in now throw to the
front and chance a go Clayton Keller he might have
taken a shot of high as well Tommy Shan Dy is not
feeling it the spinner Rama look at this play
right here on net Dylan got there finds Keller
back door and is that beautiful right onto the
tape two Beauty passes by both dery and Gunther
up top Carlson back for Crosby he chops it in you
cannot stop him you can only hope to contain him
and that is so patented Crosby this one you think
he can't do it durman's right on him too from a
impossible angle what touch what a goal Crosby
the Tang quickly across P back for Crosby back
hand Fe TA in they score it starts with s gets it
back to Chris Tang they go D to D how about that
bullet pass by Marcus P look at this a spinorama
back hand right onto the table of Jake gel Here
Comes Mard Allen finds McKinnon we know how speedy
he is got through a check McKinnon down deep with
the shot he scores Coast to Coast what a slick
little play at the Blue Line right there gets
his knee out of the way just that quick snapshot
talk about release light little move head up right
on the ice and he slides it and the hard thing for
the golender is McKinnon's just become brilliant
you never know when he's going to release the puck
and that's surprise quick but AO leaves it there
for NIS crowd getting into it NES looking for a
shot man check safe rebound they score game over
Sebastian AO wins it in overtime n just what a
move to the middle to himself fires the shot and
AO bouns it out of midair in my opinion allowed
his team to stabilizing here's McDavid beautiful
home Byer just watch McDavid go to work here this
bouncing Puck a little Cho into the neutral zone
with speed the cardian spin backand pass the
G and finishes get the paddle down wait for it
it's coming braon gets to Center Red Wings in the
midst of the change Dylan Lin on a 12 game point
streak joins Raymond Raymond right he Beauty one
Locus Raymond 45 seconds in right off the bench
what a great play by piranha to go back to Raymond
who he knew was in full gear and Piranha's at the
end of his ship oh my God what a deep did he put
on that goal tender or what and now walked Along
by twerk Jacob good move through his SL in on
goal he scores unbelievable goal by torup Cho
25 seconds in I'd say that's a super play a nice
play by tchenko to put it around his body gets
around Jadis stroble through the legs beautiful
move trouble's not able to keep his speed and
stay with him right through the crease and that'll
give an opportunity for Shay now hand it for NIS
trying to walk his way through the middle of the
rink he does he'll snap a sh well he's a one-man
speed machine in the neutral Zone when he has the
ability to rev it up and what the goenda did gor
have on the blocker side and when you do that it
can hit the inside of the blocker and go in but
that was all about the speed that he generated
a Han Solo mission in the neutral zone for that
all important first goal brought back now by stla
with kach stla in scor Tim stla does it himself
but ties the game of two wow Outside Inside
on Mika he holds off three Panthers here yeah
they converge on him because the back pressure of
mour and bosski reaches out this just pops it to
himself and he never gets the puck back that shot
never got through kov puts it up p goes in and
he what a pass by cof COV sees stammer
in behind everybody how about this move
too to fake the shot freeze the goal tender
and then cut back like that was a brilliant
move at high speed big reach does Pro and he's
able to take that puck away Smith was running
hot in the O great moves McMichael tangles in
Buckhead score C got momentum from the kill
and Conor McMichael did the rest arguably
his best goal ever in the National Hockey
League the curl and drag there the curl
and drag again and then wraps it around the
goenda Conor McMichael with speed by field around
one man in on goal scor puton Byfield what an
effort look at the footwork he kicks the puck
back to his stick you talking a big man right
there back and then able to hoist it he has to get
it over the P but when he went from the outside
to the inside I did not think he would regain
possession of the puck he surprised me and he
surprised the Blue Jackets look out here wide open
Sub Center Ice it's Patrick Kane in Chicago oh my
god with the overtime winner look at the hands and
a quick shot is almost like he's looking the other
way look at of looking for the pass no Big Goal
hands of a sergeon ends it all think a partial
change and here comes Nikolai elers kicking it
into gear plays it to himself off the board zers
to the slot shoots and he scores a masterpiece
from eers of a Del lead penalty Coast to Coast
you can literally hear his blade slashing through
the ice up here in the Press Box and he winds this
thing up 200 ft tucks this thing in off the post
36 km an hour a solo effort Nikolai elers finds
his second of the game I'm thinking Cole singer
the youngest player ever to play for the jackets
Troy Terry dangles through everybody and puts the
ducks on the board he gets those legs going in the
neutral zone and watch how many players he blows
past this guy goes right between three other Blue
Jackets and just rips it up top come back to
life is the big scen here's forer in dangles
to the back C he's what a play by Tyson forer
known for his shot and I thought maybe a good
opportunity to potentially rip it through a
screen in steady ad Li through the legs and
Surprises vasileski with a short side backand boy
what a thing of beauty that is De BR boy Tangles a
punke check P Charlie me boy wins a hit overtime
watch this move here right there and he goes for
Skinner goes for the Poke check he misses the
pot and Charlie makoy go PS right to the deck
and what a reaction what a move there shoots the
puck around P tips it to the middle Miller Chase
able to poke it ahead now he Taps itead he's got
to break away shorthanded it's m what a huge goal
for JT Miller his 30th of the Year short handed he
puts the K back on top what an unbelievable play
by Miller as he pokes the puck past Chris leang
watch the puck jump up Miller's going to knock
it down and beat Tristan jar JT Miller's been a
beast sweet mantha will drift wide cross I oetkin
snaps out on the way score off a beautiful pass
it's leier and what a play by Alexander oetkin we
always talk about his scoring prowess well what
a pass that was to find its way across the front
of the paint and laier giving a little tap to the
capitals Captain there love that gears it toward
the net and stars makes a big [Applause] save what
of the size and the strength and the balance there
from Team o Myers as he kicks that pu from his
skate to his stick and one hands this pu into the
net right here that is just great concentration
a power move in front of the Panther's neet Tren
for Yosi he drags spins around Yosi right in front
kicked up they score what a Bo by Yosi and yakar
Tren heads for the people he's TI the score look
at the magic here byos is dreading goes to the
net puts it on the back hand up and over gustus
and J Theodore starts it out Nick wad to the Blue
Line dumps it in Cross Corner SW it on that score
what a goal by Paul coner hick wad just putting
this Puck to the open area I think it was a dump
in but before it can land conter out of the air
as he swings at that one and able to get it past
the short side on San a tough one for a goenda
to read you're not expecting that great hand
eye coordination here's NZ go now surrounded
he's able to stick handle through that traffic a
still stickling driving to The N he scores a Bea
this is just a one one individual Le tce finishes
off walking right around theend what a play this
is the legs and here comes the next boo draws
it in cuts to the middle beautiful edges to keep
alive on the skates and then tucks it in the open
net for Hy for barov off his stick barov trying to
settle it down in front and they score put this
one right at the top of your list of highlight
goals for the season the individual effort the
handy coordination of Alexander barov goes off his
stick there he Taps it once Taps it twice and then
the third try he gets it over onto the stick for a
perfect tap in by Reinhardt look at that play by
barov as he's falling down oh that is pretty to
watch my goodness Elite from barov right side for
J J PKA back to Power across the line middle stack
Skinner back hand pass oh go this is some really
nice Puck movement here see them working the top
side here you get them separated a little bit
Jeff Skinner the bumper guy down low he's going
to find Kyle aoso and this is how it's supposed
to work that quick guy right there no look pass
by Skinner to aoso straight across to JJ PKA and
he got that right up top where he needed to on the
playground dribbling through everyone and off Co
out front they score well when it's your day it's
your day T Terin what a boot cuz I believe this
legally goes off of his skate boot what he did
to angle that puck with his right skate he stays
on the ice he plays it with his stick after the
fact it's malen Stein and Wilson Valenstein for
Wilson fires he hit the post rebound score boy
oh boy that second whack of the puck out of mid
air is something what a beautiful pass by melen
Stein right between the apacks of the stick and
the feet of the defenseman and there it is out
of midair H check back across the line by Kyle KH
they started the period really well oh bouncing
but score what a play Nyquist through the legs of
the trop pass to forsberg Nyquist in there he's in
allone hellu has fallen that puck all the way over
thinking nikist is going to shoot this one and a
nice little touch pass head Manning foro with
some speed drops it for the trailer paner down
low for Fox takes it to the back hand it scores
Adam fox makes it two to one New York what a
slick move from Adam Fox as he drags this around
erson to the backand and Adam Fox scores a sweet
one the Rangers quick response and a 2-1 lead for
Montreal as who we talked about they want M Andy
out against this man con m to the screwing it back
to his forehead and tuing it home for his 26th of
the Year this is an excellent Step Up by Matas e
that little poke jet keeps it alive and the turn
over and then MAV goes to work individual effort
philad York the head def Frost the line drops to
tippet tiet Def Frost and that go he SC between
the legs upstairs Morgan Frost dazzles cow a Bunga
baby oh my gosh Morgan Frost between the legs what
a pass by Owen tippet as well back to Frosty going
to the net my word Frosty what a goal four of them
out there for over a minute and a half now here's
a chance forers and he shoots and scores when you
got four guys on the ice still after a minute and
a half absolutely gased it's like they're standing
still as fly comes through the middle of the ice
at 100 mph look at him eyes up aware of everything
right there that play on the entry by the blue
line from for hand to backhand look at the time
space and he just beats Allen low that's a big one
the cat off the boards good stick mat and he sees
it satar back so he's going to try and take him
mat in short handed for it what a go unbelievable
from Magic Mike just a great read ment just jumps
on it and he says do defend me Mr Tatar good luck
and what a de with Crosby Crosby fires and a save
by remember that stop now Crosby scores on a
beautiful redirect what a play by Crosby again
this tip is unbelievable look how far wide that
puck is but that straight blade of Crosby allows
him to kind of redirect pu that to something else
my goodness gin was there to take that puck away a
chance a two on0 gold gler from p hoglander scores
a beauty two on0 and hoglander with a beautiful
play I mean he sells it on the way in and then
when he does that right here that holds the
goenda getting this game tied and a punk
rebounding score I was talking about their
face offs being good well how about that handy
work Strow will get another assist the watch one
two and up and over the goal t he definitely
is the hands guy that we know he is that was
extraordinary hands from Milano his career for
the third time last game against Chicago done
with three different teams stolen by Kango go
it's Kango what a play this is a really good
stick by kzco he just doesn't give up watch
kzo knock the stick on fa the puck comes free
and then a beautiful dangle here by kzco slot
Ben left wing side now upstairs he to Robertson
Ben Robertson again delays bed front back door
they score nice patience man what a pass what
a pass by Robertson and he finds rope hint on
the back door even that one had to rattle in a
little bit off of the skate of the Smith off
the pipe and then in again to Heron back to
suder right wing side of the go Joshua between
his legs he scores oh my word Dakota Joshua
reaches into his bag of tricks and pulls out
his 14th goal of the season and it was a beauty
two goals two assists over the devil's last
three games eer splits the KN gets the puck
back here scor oh what a move by ni heer and
we saw Mercer foral that puck he glovs it down
not easy to handle he finds Nico heer splitting
the Tron defense what a play from eer on here to
Linsky serson oh that one bang off the roll as Ry
dumps a puck to the corner here it looked like no
one really knew where was is going to go and as
Maro steals it and now quick decision off the
ear of sokin there's no daylight but somehow
Marko with the head turned of sokin gets that
puck in the back of the net incredible Terry
battling with rer Evans trailing to play nice
little play by Carlson who scores Leo Carlson a
highl now watch this play by Carlson through his
own legs back to himself and the shot is perfect
gets it away in a hurry and just snaps it up top
final minute of the second watch out McKinnon's
got wheels McKinnon's going to go right around
Middleton here he comes again hello here come the
hatch seventh career hatrick and it was a thing
of beauty highlighting everything that makes him
great the explosiveness the East West the dynamic
play Puck comes up high recognizes and then he
just absolutely takes off get with the race to
lose PL over for shle comes here's valard oh what
a goal G valard back between his speak just an
outstanding recovery of a pu from sea monad and
he allows valard to do that between the legs it's
almost magical he does this often teams know
it they pre-out it but they can't stop it that
is unbelievable fetchik off with it he'll dance
around he'll travle across move it he thinks he
had a goal I think he had a goal we'll wait for a
review if we get a horn get this we might hear a
buzzer from the leag here it is beautiful lross go
number three oh is this ever stylish what a play
and he's got that stick coming from Peak peak's
ready for it this is just marvelous quickness with
his hands Nikita COV dishes off to point points
the give to COV great pass back Ander Stone the
spin around you think it's a no look pass but if
you look really closely out of the corner of his
eye he'll take a look into the middle then he
spins around measures it knows where everybody
is and it's right on the tape to Connor Sher cuz
when you play with 86 just get ready it's coming
ell sends it ahead for o Conor making a move
through Maran through car scores turnover by
makoy in the offensive zone that puck has to go
deep when it doesn't ' Conor recognizes that Brad
maran's the only defender back he pushes it by
Maran uses his size and speed and scores a beauty
guys for a rookie of the year Lucas Reel with a
step on the loose Puck reel great speed there by
Reel and then when cut into the middle of the ice
he protected the puck calber thought that he was
going to go to the forehand instead he cuts back
to the backand and this is a dazzling move right
here forehand backand thanks for coming what a
play that is right there screaming across what a
stop what pan across Lin G the spare pan cuts to
the middle now L Raymond chance to shoot what a
keep in by Shane gos to spare I gu and time again
they've been blocked when he did get chances and
he now gets rewarded with a minute and 17 to go
oh my oh my that first sickeness that's for sure
30 goal season he dishes and now McDavid has
it McDavid comes into the Zone he's wheeling
and dealing McDavid pass front the shot is going
the score Conor McDavid who else he gets it set
up what a good spinner we've seen him do that
before it doesn't matter you've seen him do it
before how do you contain it to br Lucid room
to head up by the David looking like he's going
to pass the SP around Anderson and then he finds H
humps at home for a one nothing Le forever [Music]
here's dangling by just the creativity gets
down on one knee as he puts it between his
legs and now you've got San down and unable to
rec he was expecting a backand shot right off
the bat instead kept his feet moving Crea that
lane and has given this building some life off
the boards it comes up on the wing a long
lead pass for Matthews Matthews is in alone
scar holy me big papy has given the leap the
lead this is just a heck of a pass here by Max
doy that hang time pass was perfectly placed
behind the defenseman backhand forehand hmark
went hard for the Deep to the right Kee
to kobitar kobar back in front Kee score
tipped in Adrien Kee it's deflected once twice
it has to be below the height of the crossbar
I think they've already determined that yeah no
problem there whatsoever but that's a 200 foot
shift by Adrien kempen these overtime games end
on a strange bounce or rebound send it to the net
and get people to the net lenol right wi Corner
poster knock is there he scores Riley is beat to
the Pucket took a bounce in an angle going right
to the net it worked out perfect perfectly for
pastor knock to skate onto the puck he turns
to the net and the agility and quickness to
go forehand backhand and in Mar one man breakout
none better here he comes a shot K coost to Coast
k m you got to be kidding me he say I'll do it
myself all the way down Broadway to the outside
and he rips it home that was simply amazing grabs
it and then just six one pop shelf right under the
bar he's got it behind his own neck zedora passes
to Center for Joshua drops to G with speed right
wing M the on their Zone takes a shot takes a shot
he stars are you kidding me conter Garland with
a complete fake out of Steward Skinner gives the
conects the lead Big Shot forses Skinner to slide
over to his left and Darin he sneaky good hands
there makes a great read and slides it between the
legs Rangers win the face off tro right Circle
downlo rer to Zan he scores M Zan it's a power
play go this ranger Power Play can sing the puck
around like very few in the league he doesn't even
have to look no chance for Freddy Anderson this is
a thing of beauty trouba at the red line stops it
left side of laier sends it in round the boards
it goes missed by oloff play it score score yes
yes the Rangers win it in overtime and lead the
series three games to none Miller back to lindol
and Hughes Miller calls for it looks in front Lind
scores oh how about lindol heast skateboarded on
the puck for about a foot and a half as he had
it under his blade what a great play under his
skate kicks it and then pass the Stick of Stewart
Skinner that is not easy to do and Cent Hollow
to the SC what a beauty that is his best b as
a member of the Edmonton ERS drle HS up H full
flight all the way one of the puck he called for a
defeat Alias Pon just in Cent ice and then walked
the d k marar takes it away Mar around one now
gets around second again here SC oh kale kale
kale marar activated from the point steered around
Sean threw it on net he went through the legs of
vinger and in and the Avalanche have a two goal
lead here in Dallas laier flying again lafranier
beautiful move and he scores oh what a goal by
Alexi laier this is highlight real stuff laier a
rush that you dream about as he drags this around
kulakov the tow drag will put him into the middle
of the ice and Alexi lafrenier is giv the Rangers
a 32 lead a brilliant individual effort down for
McDavid there is Dr settle watched carefully by
Lindell across M David moves to the outside works
his what nothing you talk about awesomeness it's
right here folks the quick little stick handle
he goes around Hast watchs the move the pull
the back and the forehand backand rof that is
an unbelievable goal on the power play for Conor
McDavid great players do great things things and
that's exactly what that was steel got burned
hening got burned and then a beautifully placed
backhand shot in the top half of the net what a
goal by McDavid up The Far Side didn't get the
clear for haggy gives barov darts in makes a Nifty
move and he scores wow barov what a goal that was
and he gets the Panthers on the board he takes a
nice feed from fori and barov uses patience and
his Long Reach H McDavid the first there everever
to score Stanley Cup final goal in the building
gra sprled away scores what a brilliant piece of
work cter McDavid with another highlight re play
watch Cory Perry he comes on the ice just trying
to stay invisible stays along the boards and then
times this perfectly four guys watching 97 why
not because you're having a hard time taking
the puck off of them look at the quick little
hands protection of the stick and then up and